# Hiu Mei Fu

## **UX / UI Designer**

Motivated UI/UX designer with a combination of skills in product design, computer science, and other related fields. Skilled in creating user-friendly experience, and well-versed in coding. Known for being self-initiative, well-organized, and a strong collaborator.

North York, CA +1 (437) 552-0215 meifu.wk@gmail.com https://meirosey.github.io/

Eligible holder of Open Work Permit Available immediately

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Orange Data Limited — UX/UI & Graphic Designer

Mar 2022 - Nov 2022, Hong Kong | Dec 2022 - Present, Remote

Capstone Project - Design interface for 'World Cup' gamemode for World Entertainment casino

- Designs various product interfaces, including web and mobile
- Creates user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and mockups
- Collaborates with cross-functional teams to implementation user-centered designs
- Creates marketing and promotional materials

# **Semeiotics Group (Asia) Limited**— Junior Web Designer

Mar 2021 - Nov 2021, Hong Kong

- Designed the layout, color scheme, and overall appearance of a website
- Implemented the design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & CMS

## **SenMedia Limited** — *Technical Artist*

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022, Freelance

Capstone Project - Acted as leader for government website revamp. Optimized information architecture

- Created visually appealing and engaging designs that meet the needs of projects, such as website, installations mobile games
- Collaborated with various teams, including developers, project managers, stakeholders and clients

### **EDUCATION**

# **City University Of Hong Kong, Hong Kong** — Bachelor Of Science In Creative Media

Aug 2015 - Oct 2019

Focus: UX/UI Design | Computer Science | Creative Media

### **SKILLS**

UX Design / Research

Design Persona & Scenario
Information Architecture
Interaction & Visual Design
Wireframing & Prototyping
Journey Map
Data Visualization
Contextual Inquiry Interview
Survey Affinity Analysis
Competitive Analysis

#### **TOOLKIT**

**Design Tools** 

**Usability Testing** 

Figma, Sketch, Adobe suits (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects etc.)

**Programing Tools** 

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Google UX Design Professional Certificate, Coursera | Google

Credential ID: 9JDNBHW3KQ9P

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing, Google

Credential ID: 3EH DR6 67L

### **AWARDS**

**Hong Kong ICT Awards 2020** - Certification of Merit, Student Innovation

### **LANGUAGES**

English, Mandarin, Cantonese - Fluent Japanese - Intermediate